{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "________ caused the fire?",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "Whom",
      "c": "What",
      "d": "Which",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- What: used to ask for information or for someone's opinion",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jonathan,_______ of these two ways is the best?",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "what",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ was that beautiful car you were driving yesterday?",
      "a": "Whom",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "Whose",
      "d": "Who",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ foot did you kick the ball with?",
      "a": "Whose",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Whom",
      "d": "Which",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who _______ you that?",
      "a": "told",
      "b": "said",
      "c": "did tell",
      "d": "did say",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Who(the subject): used to ask or talk about which person is involved, or what the name of a person is \n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whom are you talking ________?",
      "a": "for",
      "b": "to",
      "c": "after",
      "d": "in",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- We often use \"Talk to somebody\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ is that little dog?",
      "a": "Which",
      "b": "Who",
      "c": "Whom",
      "d": "Whose",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who were you talking ________?",
      "a": "about",
      "b": "for",
      "c": "after",
      "d": "of",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- We often say \" talk about somebody/something\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you see that mansion? _______ is it?",
      "a": "Which",
      "b": "Whose",
      "c": "Whom",
      "d": "Who",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Whose: used to ask which person or people a particular thing belongs to\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What _______ the explosion?",
      "a": "did cause",
      "b": "did caused",
      "c": "caused",
      "d": "cause",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- What: used to ask for information or for someone's opinion\n+ Ask for Subject: What + Verb\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "48",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}